Hello guys, today we are going to show you
how we can apply for ICICI Lombard's Mediclaim through the process.
Friends, before this I have
made a video on how to fill its form
and how we
can apply for Mediclaim by filling that form.
Friends, now I
want to give you more information in some details. So friends,
if you have any complaint regarding Mediclaim,
you can comment me
in the comment box or friends, you
can also email me. You can
request me as per your wish.
So friends, see,
I was also facing some problem in this video, that is why
friends, I made a video. So friends,
if we had to do anything for Mediclaim, friends, first
we had to pay the hospitalization bill, doctor's bills
etc. and
friends, if we mean sonography or
CT scan, friends,
we had to require a lot of documents. So
friends, earlier there was a way in which
we could do this through posts.  In which
friends, mother, by going to the post office, we fill in the
whole thing, that is, choli plate raita, friends, in this
we click on this document etc., we
also get the situation in the office for mediclaim, so
friends, how is it now, the
English people don, friends, now schools have
made it, in which friends it is always seen
that if we have to
click on mail, then friends together
asked because of friends, then we cannot send it, so
friends, they have made a new method and
friends, right now this is too much for that,
friends, I want to tell you
how to do it, so friends, first of all, let
me tell you that see friends, I have
opened the screen here, Aadhar card
cancellation check, if friends,
if we do this through the company, hospital,
distance hospital, medical here,
and friends, if it is done, then
its reset report,
friends, I have given the report here
and friends, the yellow main
bill amount of medical, I have also scanned it here and
uploaded the entire document, and
friends, the form of mediclaim is the same as
I had filled,
friends, I have scanned it here and uploaded it on this,
you can see  There are two
photos etc. pasted here and here
friends my PAN card so friends
after scanning this we have to click on the
file and the name of the file means
if I have
folded it towards Aadhar card here then friends
here I will give Aadhar if cancel check
if it is of the company then friends here
friends in this way give the names of all these documents
to the file so that friends who will check it further,
any senior that is bank
employee and they do not have any problem in understanding it so
friends now this will be
about the document so friends there was another
update that the size of the document friends
that size should not be more than 10 MB
friends this update is very important
if its size is more than 2 inches that means 10 MB then
friends we cannot apply it
so friends we have
seen here by using low resolution I have
found the name of this folder and friends you can see
what is the size of the file here the husband has
seen many of which it is 274 also 263 also
282 so friends like this  I have selected its
size in the queue, that is, its orientation, and friends, if we right click here, then
in the properties, we will
see how many inches this file has,
friends, friends, our size is 5.41 MB, so friends, this
is so long and it should be less than 10 MB,
friends, then you mean, there may be a
problem in editing the documents,
or it can still happen, so friends, now we will
learn how to fix them,
friends, this method is very easy, and friends,
I don't know if it can last for so long,
because during this they made it, so
friends, the method of making holes, so friends, they
appointed
friends, Healthcare Airtel,
ICICI Lombard Doctor and friends, we have appointed
Amazon in C, which friends,
we mean our company,
friends, if you have any problem, then you
can contact directly and
subscribe, and friends, this is what I have said in this,
and friends, now we will complete
this entire process, we will subscribe and send an
email, so friends, we get the result
immediately, that is, in the school,
we subscribe and
after a few days, we get another
tracking data.  Friends,
after getting it, we mean skin and it gets
deposited in our bank, so friends, this is a very
easy method and friends, I have used
scrub and friends, if you have any of your
relatives, friends, your friends, family, you
can share this information with them
and friends, if you like this video of mine, then
friends, you
can like, share and subscribe to my channel, so
friends, this was all for today, thank you.